reknew.org 2019-02-07

# Privacy Policy - Greg Boyd - ReKnew

(effective as of June 30, 2012)

ReKnew respects the privacy concerns of the visitors to ReKnew.org (the “Website”). As a general policy, no personal information is automatically collected from users of the site. In the event that we do collect any personally identifiable data about visitors to this site, that information is only collected on a voluntary basis, and it is only known to ReKnew.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you cannot agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the Website.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of ReKnew.org by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

**I. THE TYPE OF INFORMATION THE WEBSITE COLLECTS**

The Website may collect personal information with your knowledge and consent. For instance, when you complete a survey, make a purchase, donate to ReKnew, subscribe to a newsletter, or register for any portion of our services, you may be asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name, address or phone number. Additional information such as your age or gender may also be requested.

Certain non-personal information of visitors is recorded by the standard operation of ReKnew’s Internet servers, including without limitation the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, the website that referred you, and the domain name of the visitor’s Internet service provider.

**II. HOW THE WEBSITE USES INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU**

ReKnew uses this information to provide you with the service you have requested. For instance, if you subscribe to any of our publications we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice and your mailing address to send you the publication. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, services, and/or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs.

All such personal information is retained by ReKnew and is not sold or otherwise transferred outside the company unless we obtain your express consent to do so or if we are required by law or by court/governmental order to disclose such information in a particular circumstance. This data, in aggregate, non-personally-identifying form, may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses. If you do not wish to receive further communications from us by e-mail, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail.

**III. COOKIES**

This site also uses “cookies,” which are pieces of information that are transferred to an individual user’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. ReKnew never uses cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie and the cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information. Cookies function by saving your passwords and site preferences – and as a result, it is possible to speed up your future activities at our site and allow us to provide you information specifically tailored to your interests. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it may be possible that some parts of the site will not function optimally if you do so.

**IV. CHILDREN AND PARENTS**

This website is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. In compliance with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, no personal information (including name, mailing address, telephone number and email address) will be collected from any visitor under the age of 13. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must first obtain verifiable consent from the parent or legal guardian before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this site. Parents or legal guardians may provide ReKnew with consent to collect such information by e-mail, by facsimile or by postal mail at the number/addresses set forth below under “Contact Us.”

You should consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help supervise your children’s online activities. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing their name, address, and other personal information online without parental permission.

If you’re worried about your children’s activities or their privacy on our site, we encourage you to contact us as described below.

**V. CONTACT**

If you have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, [you may contact us here.](https://reknew.org/engage/)
